no matter the distance
no matter how years turn
love takes flight with a promise of return
it circles the world it knows where to land
still warm in the touch of a welcoming hand
boomerang of love
a flight never lost
through shadows and storms
it still makes its course
each time it is cast it will rise far above
returning again the boomerang of love
eternal boomerang to hearts that are warm
to the unlove
the gentle the kind and the storm and above
all return with the truth from above
to restore what was given
return as love
boomerang of love
of lfight never lost
through shadows and storms
it still makes its course
each time it is cast it will rise far above
returning again the boomerang of love
through the arc of the sky
and the breath of the earth
love finds the lost
and rekindles their work
no force can deter
no shadow can stay
the path of love's promise
will find its own way
boomerang of love
a flight never lost
through shadows and storms
it still makes its
each time it is cast
it will rise far above
returning again the boomerang of love
boomerang of love
forever it circles
forever it flies beneath the sun
through unending skies
boomerang of love
in its endless return
the fire keeps glowing
the heart's ever burned